boats.net 2009-09-18

# Privacy Policy

Site Security  
The OutdoorNetwork recognizes that privacy is a serious matter. This Policy pertains to all of the services, products, and websites offered by the OutdoorNetwork or its subsidiaries or affiliated companies. We take several steps to safeguard all information provided to us by you. This document focuses on the different types of personal information we collect when using the OutdoorNetwork services.

Sharing of Data  
The OutdoorNetwork does not participate in information sharing. Your personal information never gets sold or rented to any third party services under any circumstances. We provide information only to the affiliated companies with the network (the OutdoorNetwork listing). We require that all parties agree and adhere to the process and are in compliance with this Policy and all other confidential security measures.

If you have any questions concerning this Policy, please feel free to contact us via email [info@outdoornetwork.com](mailto:outdoornetwork.com) or write to us at:

**The OutdoorNetwork  
c/o Privacy Policy  
730 US Hwy 27 N,  
Lake Placid, FL 33852 **

How Your Personal Information is Used  
The OutdoorNetwork does not require you to register for an account on any of the affiliate websites. You can browse all sites without having an account, but you will be required to create one when purchasing a product or if you decide to take advantage of certain features, such as Wish List and other selected services. We may inquire you to confirm your personal information if you decide to contact our Customer Service department to protect your confidentiality by verifying your identity.

Customer Provided Information  
When you register for an account, we ask you for personal information (such as your name, email address and an account password). For certain services, we also ask for credit card or other payment account information, which we preserve in encrypted form on our secure servers. We gather this information in order to bill you for your purchase. Your address is also needed to allow us to ship your product to the specified destination. We may merge the information you present under your account with information from other OutdoorNetwork services in order to provide you with an enhanced experience and to advance the worth of our services. When you create an account, you can elect to save your billing information in Your Account . Please know this information can be changed or= deleted except in certain instances when it is required to obtain a specific type of an account.

Computer Information  
When you visit any of the OutdoorNetwork affiliates, you will be assigned a permanent cookie that is a tiny file containing a string of characters to your computer that distinctively identifies your browser. We use these cookies to enhance the quality of our service by tracking user trends and storing user preferences, such as how people search. These features include storing your shopping cart for later viewing. You can reset your browser to decline all cookies or to designate when a cookie is being sent; however, most browsers are originally set up to accept cookies. Please note that some of the OutdoorNetwork services and features may not function appropriately if your cookies are disabled.

Customer Inquires or Requests  
When any form of communication (email, fax, etc.) are received by any affiliates of the OutdoorNetwork we may retain those documents in order to process your requests, respond to inquires, and enhance our services. We may also communicate special promotions and selected featured items to you.

Affiliated sites  
This policy applies to services and web sites that are owned and operated by the OutdoorNetwork.

Security Measures  
We take suitable security procedures to protect against unlawful access or destruction of the stored data. These include in-house reviews of our data gathering, storage, security measures, and processing practices, as well as central security methods to guard against unauthorized access to systems where we house personal information. Please do not share your account password with anyone. Other than on the OutdoorNetwork sites, we will never ask you for your password.

We control access to personal information to all employees, agents, and contractors who need to know the information to operate, grow, or enhance our services. These individuals are bound by confidentiality obligations and may be subject to regulation, including termination and criminal prosecution, if they fail to conform to these obligations.

Your Privacy  
We realize that making purchases on any website requires trust on your part. We know the significance of your trust and value that very highly and vow to you, our customer, that we will always work to safeguard any and all personal information that you provide to us and that it will only be ued as set forth in this Policy.

Changes to Policy  
This Privacy Policy was last update on January 5, 2007. We do reserve the privilege to modify, change or amend this policy at any time. Please check our Policy periodically for any changes. The use of the OutdoorNetwork and all affiliates after revision implies that you consent to this Privacy Policy as modified.
